Bavaria
Marist College
Bavaria
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.1.2
1203 linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Bavaria
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - Bavaria, 2.1.1.1.2
              - Promenade along the Isar showing bicycle path and bridle path, Munich, before 1916; 36 (Box 1173)
                5x7
              - Chiemsee from a distance, before 1916; 37
              - Königs-See, southern end of lake, before 1916; 38
              - Chalet on the southwest bank of the lake, Königs-See, before 1916; 39
              - Königs-See, Obersee in the distance, before 1916; 40
              - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in front of fountain, Schloss Linderhof gardens, before 1916; 41
              - Fountain in play, Schloss Linderhof gardens, before 1916; 42
              - Looking toward chateau from the Monopteros, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 43
                film
              - Front view of chateau and grape arbors taken from below the Monopteros, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 44
              - General view of chateau and gardens from Monopteros, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 45
              - Looking toward the Monopteros, Linderhof gardens, before 1916; 46
              - Schloss Linderhof, taken from hill behind chateau and showing rear of building and formal gardens, before 1916; 47
              - Formal gardens and rear of chateau looking toward mountains, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 48
              - Rear of chateau showing trees and mountains, taken from grape arbor, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 49
              - Rear view of chateau with Louis XV garden, Schloss Linderhof, before 1916; 50
              - Looking down on grape arbor, Schloss Linderhof gardens, before 1916; 51
              - Moorish kiosk, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 52
                4x5
              - Silver cabinet, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 53
              - Hall of mirrors, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 54
              - Kiosk, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 55
              - Dining room, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 56
              - Pink cabinet, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 57
              - Blue cabinet, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 58
              - Bedchamber, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 59
              - Audience chamber, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 60
              - Western tapestry chamber, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 61
              - Painting, Schloss Linderhof[?], copy, 7/1/1910; 1 (Box 1174)
              - Tannhäuser in Venus Grotto, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 2
              - Venus Grotto, Schloss Linderhof, copy, 7/1/1910; 3
              - Detail of the Feldherrnhalle, Munich, before 1916; 4
              - Woman tending street can switch, Munich, before 1916; 5
              - Playground of children, Munich, before 1916; 6
              - Ox cart, Fern Pass Road, before 1916; 7
              - Near Fern Pass, before 1916; 8
              - Steep road near Fern Pass, before 1916; 9
              - Road to Ober-Ammergan, before 1916; 10
              - Little church near Füssen, before 1916; 11
              - Pastoral scene near Füssen, before 1916; 12
              - Valley near Füssen, before 1916; 13
              - Tree avenue near Füssen, before 1916; 14
              - Stock waiting for the Clumee[?] boat, before 1916; 15
              - Boat with Frank R. Roberson and party on the lake, Königs-See, before 1916; 16
              - Saint Bartholomew in the chapel[?] of S.S. John and Paul, Königs-See, before 1916; 17
              - Motorboat on Königs-See, before 1916; 18
              - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson and peasant girl at Königs-See, before 1916; 19
              - Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on rock at southern end of Königs-See, before 1916; 20
              - Bavaria’s country church, before 1916; 21
              - Hotel at Schongau, before 1916; 22
              - Little village with quaint church, before 1916; 23
              - Country church, before 1916; 24
              - Showing German architecture in residences, Munich, before 1916; 25
              - Wittlesbader Brühe[?] (statue of Otho von Wittlesbach), Munich, before 1916; 26
              - Bridges over the Isar, Munich, before 1916; 27
              - Church of Saint Luke, Munich, before 1916; 28
              - Fish fountain, Munich, copy, 7/1/1910; 29
              - Ruhmeshalle, Hall of Fame, Munich, copy, 7/1/1910; 30
              - Hofbräuhaus beer hall, Munich, copy, 7/1/1910; 31
              - New town hall, Munich, copy, 7/1/1910; 32
              - Frauenkirch towers, Munich, copy, 7/1/1910; 33
              - Bedchamber, Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 34
              - Salon, Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 35
              - Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 36
              - Corridor on the first floor, Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 37
              - Throne Hall, Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 38
              - Throne Hall, Schloss Neuschwanstein, copy, 7/1/1910; 39
              - Town scene, clock tower and statue, copy, 7/1/1910; 40
              - Small gallery, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 7/1/1910; 41
              - State staircase, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 6/1/1910; 42
              - Great Hall of Mirrors, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 7/1/1910; 43
              - State bedchamber, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 7/1/1910; 44
              - Writing room, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 7/1/1910; 45
              - Bedroom, Schloss Herrenchiemsee, copy, 7/1/1910; 46
              - Albrecht Dürer’s house, Nuremberg, copy, 7/1/1910; 47
              - Topplerhaus, Nuremberg, copy, 7/1/1910; 48
              - Schnitzerschule, Oberammergau, copy, before 1916; 49
              - Stilfserjoch Strasse, Franzenshöhe, copy, 7/1/1910; 50
              - View of town, mountains in background, copy, 7/1/1910; 51
              - König Ludwig, copy, 7/1/1910; 52
              - Old man, copy, 7/1/1910; 53
              - Photograph of man by E. Bieber, copy, 3/2/1915; 54
              - Daily feeding of children in Berlin whose fathers are at the front, copy, 3/2/1915; 55
              - View of town, mountains in background, copy, before 1916; 56